# TAYLOR FINKLEA

## DEVOPS AND INFRASTRUCTURE MANAGER

## CONTACT

Kansas City, KS 66109 taylor.finklea@gmail.com

https://taylor.finklea.io

https://www.linkedin. com/in/taylorfinklea-8614238b/

## QUALIFICATIONS

- Management and Leadership
- 10 years of IT Experience
- 4 years of DevOps Experience
- Kubernetes and Helm
- Azure Management
- SOC II Type II Audit
- Frontend and Backend Development
- Active Directory and Group Policy
- MDM
- Powershell and Bash Scripting
- Azure Sentinel

## ATTRIBUTES

- Management
- Leadership
- Eagle Scout
- Organized
- Dependable
- · Eager to Learn
- Hard-Working

### CERTS/AWARDS

CompTia A+ CompTia Network+ Site Development Associate CIW

**Computer Technology** Sterling Scholar

Woods Cross High School

## PROFILE

I have a variety of experience and am the Manager of DevOps, Infrastructure and Information Security in my current role. I manage internal Infrastructure, DevOps, Kubernetes, Automation, MDM, SIEM, Audit, IT Budget, Azure Cloud and all other systems. I mentor and train members of my team.

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## **DevOps and Infrastructure Manager**

Lumifi Cyber Inc | Feb 2019 - Present

- Duties include Architecting Scalable DevOps, Management, Audits, Infrastructure, Infosec
- Architected fully scalable infrastructure using Azure DevOps, Terraform, Helm, Kubernetes, Packer, Windows Virtual Desktop, Azure App Gateway, Azure WAF, Azure Firewall, Azure Virtual WAN, Azure ADDS
- Organized and completed many large-scale projects, such as a full data center migration to Azure
- Manage departments of DevOps, Infrastructure and Information Security
- Working with:

Node.js

- Management/Leadership
  DevSecOps Kubernetes o Helm Charts Github Actions Rancher Agile Methodology Github Codespaces CI/CD Pipelines Azure DevOps o AKS/EKS/GKE o K3s/RKE2 Docker o Terraform o Packer o Ansible o Git Vagrant Microsoft Azure/AWS/GCP Prometheus o Cloudflare
- Microsoft 365 Active Directory/Azure AD Grafana
- Windows Servers o Azure CLI Linux/Linux Servers System/Network Admin Tailscale TypeScript/JavaScript Bash/PowerShell

Postgresql/Mysql/Influxdb

 Change Management ○ SOC II Type II

#### Systems Administrator / Project Manager

Executech Inc. | Aug 2017 - Feb 2019

- IT consultant working for multiple government clients
- Duties include Systems Administrator, Network Administrator, Information Security, Linux Administrator
- Managing large-scale projects
- Preparing clients for large-scale email migrations, domain migrations, and firewall migrations

# **Support Engineer**

DigiCert Inc. | Aug 2015 - Aug 2017

- Assigned SSL Certificates, Client Certificates, and Code Signing
- Installed, troubleshot, and configured web servers such as IIS, Apache, and Tomcat
- Answered customer chats, emails, and phone calls

#### IT Support Technician

Dixie State University | Nov 2014 - Aug 2015

- Answered calls, voicemails, emails for Helpdesk and for Tech Support line
- Took on work orders for customer problems, set up appointments and fixed issues
- Re-mirrored and set up new computers and equipment.

### **Remote Desktop Support Technician**

ManagerPlus Solutions | Mar 2014 - Apr 2015

- Answered technical calls and emails
  - Troubleshot servers, networks, and our software